

Professional Summary

I am a highly motivated and skilled software developer with five years of professional experience and a record of spearheading the development of important software projects. I would like to grow in to a technical leadership role.

Education

University of Ottawa, Ottawa, Ontario

Master of Science - Mathematics

Fall 2015 - Summer 2017

Thesis The Convex Hull of the Highest Weight Orbit and the Carathéodory Orbitope

Carleton University, Ottawa

BSc - Mathematics and Computer Science

Fall 2010 - January 2015

11.92/12 GPA

Honours Project Torsion Points on Elliptic Curves

Technical Skills

Languages and technical skills:

- Strong Python skills
- Strong C/C++ skills
- Strong debugging skills (gdb, valgrind)
- OOP programming
- Solid foundations in computer science
- Experience deploying machine learning models
- Version control (git)

Dev-ops and automation:

- Containers: Docker and Kubernetes
- Jenkins
- Apache Airflow
- Make and CMake

Other skills:

- Flex and Bison
- The LLVM framework
- Embedded development: some experience with NXP IMX and Raspberry Pi pico
- $\bullet~$ Some experience with X86 and ARM assembly language

Experience

SociVolta

November 2019 - April 2023

Montreal, QC

Senior Software Developer

- Responsible for building a large part of the company's trading platform, including: CI/CD (Jenkins, Docker, Kubernetes) and ETL (Apache Airflow, Python)
- Responsible for development of key trading tools, including an interpreter for a domain specific language which we used to express our trading strategies using Python and Pandas
- Mentoring junior members

$\mathbf{ZeligSoft}$

January 2018 - November 2019

 $Software\ Developer$

Gatineau, QC

- Development and maintenance code generation tool for OpenSplice DDS: Tool written in C which translated OMG IDL into language-specific stubs
- Development and maintenance of JavaScript bindings for OpenSplice DDS
- Maintenance of Python bindings for OpenSplice DDS
- Maintenance of OpenSplice build system (CMake, Jenkins)